KIERSTEN LILLIS

1005 Harmon Place, Longmont, CO 80501 · 317.752.0887

kierstenlillis@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/kierstenlillis · https://kierstenlillis.com/video

I am a dedicated communication professional who excels in both new and traditional media. I have a diverse range of experience in strategic content creation and implementation, including audio, video, print, written, and multimedia formats. Whatever the medium, I work with my clients to bring their vision to life and help them achieve their goals.

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2017 - PRESENT / MARKETING & MEDIA, RED IDEA PARTNERS

- Social media & email marketing
- Content creation audio, video, blog posts, newsletters, print media, press releases
- Project management, coordination, and organization

JUNE 2014 - JUNE 2016 / SENIOR VIDEO EDITOR, VIDEOMAGIC PRODUCTIONS/HIGHWAY MEDIA INC.

- Edited wedding films, nonprofit event recaps, video workshop series, multi-video promotional package
- Owned editing process and client communication from start to finish

OCTOBER 2013 - APRIL 2014 / MEDIA PRODUCER, LUXOTTICA RETAIL NORTH AMERICA

- Produced/project-managed brand videos and live events
- Managed timelines, talent, and client deliverables

MARCH 2013 – APRIL 2014 / MARKETING ASSISTANT, CRADLE NORTH AMERICA INC.

- Organized trade-show visits, technical training sessions; prepared materials
- Managed Salesforce customer database and Constant Contact email newsletters

EDUCATION

MAY 2012 / B.A. COMMUNICATION & B.A. FRENCH, UNIVERSITY OF DAYTON

Double Major. Communication concentration in Electronic Media. Double Minor in Psychology and Film Studies. Graduated Summa Cum Laude. 2012 recipient of the Bette Rogge Morse Award to the Outstanding Senior Woman in Communication

JULY 2011 / STUDY ABROAD, UNIVERSITE CATHOLIQUE DE L'OUEST

One-month intensive French program in both French language and culture

SKILLS/SAMPLES

- Demo Reel and Video Samples: https://kierstenlillis.com/video/#work-samples
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Content creation
- Website content management

- Excellent oral and written communication skills
- Strong organizational and time-management skills
- Ability to manage multiple tasks
- Social media management
- Literate in both Mac and Windows

OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Blogging 2008-2012 for the University of Dayton Dept. of Enrollment Management; various others 2008-present
- Theatre stage performance 2008-present